Where do we begin.
A year ago, these cops and lawyers wouldn't dare cross any of you. I mean, what happened ?
So what are you proposing? It's simple. Kill the Batman.
Here's my card.
Bruce, this is Harvey Dent.
Rachel's told me everything about you.
Well, I certainly hope not.
You once told me that we'd be together
Did you mean it ?
Bruce, don't make me your only hope for a normal life.
You're Alfred, right ? That's right sir.
Any psychotic ex-boyfriends I should be worried about ?
Oh, you have no idea.
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen.
We are tonight's entertainment.
Well hello, beautiful.
You look nervous.
I've seen now what I have to become to stop men like him.
The night is darkest just before the dawn.
I promise you, the dawn is coming.
And here we go.
Come on !
This city deserves a better class of criminal.
And I'm gonna give it to 'em.
Noo !
You'll see. I'll show you.
You either die a hero, or you live long enough to see yourself become the villain.
Will you be wanting the Batpod, sir ?
In the middle of the day, Alfred ? Not very subtle.
The Lamborghini, then ?
Much more subtle.